

## Profile

Two years of experience as a software engineer in the full development life cycle and four years as a game software tester. Able to effectively selfmanage, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Seeking a role where I can apply my skills and meaningfully contribute to the organization while growing professionally.

# Employment History

SDET II (Software Development Engineer in Test)

**Experis Game Solutions** 

August 2022 – December 2022

Tempe, AZ

Briefly worked as a developer in test for Age of Empires 4.

- Created a tool to simulate combat scenarios to produce game balance data.
- Fixed and added functionality to a game play bot automation tool.

#### **Test Associate III**

**Experis Game Solutions** 

November 2018 to July 2022

Tempe, AZ

Worked as a tester for The Master Chief Collection

- Coordinating with the team to execute test plans and other self-directed testing
- Writing bugs in Azure DevOps and verifying fixes
- Writing task reports summarizing test coverage and results
- Training new members assigned to the same team on project processes and standards

#### Software Engineer II

**General Dynamics Mission Systems** 

August 2014 to October 2016

Scottsdale, AZ

Worked on maintaining software for a satellite 3G network in C++ within a Solaris environment.

- Implementing fixes, unit testing, reviewing code, and writing test plans for test team verification of fixed bugs
- Revising version description and installation documentation and creating an installer for a subsystem used at site
- Maintaining and creating new tools to parse and correlate data in logs received daily from the deployed site to detect issues and monitor system health
- Evaluating and assisting with issues found by the test team

### Education

**B.S. Computer Science** 

May 2014 - 3.83 GPA

**Arizona State University** 

Tempe, AZ

The Web Developer Bootcamp

www.udemy.com

2019

**Introduction to Databases** 

www.coursera.org

April 2023

A course by Meta

## Details

Phoenix, Arizona
623-498-9313
JaronLifsey@gmail.com
Portfolio

## Skills

C++
C#
Java

OOP Principles

Software Testing

HTML, CSS, Type Script

GIT

Agile

SQL / Databases

### Soft Skills

Self-Directed

Communication

Critical Thinking